<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<QuotesCollection>
  <FinanceQuote>
    <Quote>Money is a terrbile master but an excellent servant.</Quote>
    <Author>P.T Barnum</Author>
  </FinanceQuote>
  <FinanceQuote>
    <Quote>Beware of little expenses; a small leak will sink a great ship.</Quote>
    <Author>Benjamin Franklin</Author>
  </FinanceQuote>
  <FinanceQuote>
    <Quote>The desire of gold is not for gold. It is for the means of freedom and benefit.</Quote>
    <Author>Ralph Waldo Emerson</Author>
  </FinanceQuote>
  <FinanceQuote>
    <Quote>An investment in knowledge pays the best interest.</Quote>
    <Author>Benjamin Franklin</Author>
  </FinanceQuote>
  <FinanceQuote>
    <Quote>I will tell you the secret to getting rich on Wall Street. You try to be greedy when others are fearful. And you try to be fearful when others are greedy.</Quote>
    <Author>Warren Buffett</Author>
  </FinanceQuote>
  <FinanceQuote>
    <Quote>Formal education will make you a living; self-education will make you a fortune.</Quote>
    <Author>Jim Rohn</Author>
  </FinanceQuote>
  <FinanceQuote>
    <Quote>Money is only a tool. It will take you wherever you wish, but it will not replace you as the driver.</Quote>
    <Author>Ayn Rand</Author>
  </FinanceQuote>
  <FinanceQuote>
    <Quote>Buy when everyone else is selling and hold until everyone else is buying. That’s not just a catchy slogan. It’s the very essence of successful investing.</Quote>
    <Author>J. Paul Getty</Author>
  </FinanceQuote>
  <FinanceQuote>
    <Quote>How many millionaires do you know who have become wealthy by investing in savings accounts? I rest my case.</Quote>
    <Author>Robert G. Allen</Author>
  </FinanceQuote>
  <FinanceQuote>
    <Quote>Wealth is the ability to fully experience life.</Quote>
    <Author>Henry David Thoreau</Author>
  </FinanceQuote>
  <FinanceQuote>
    <Quote>You must gain control over your money or the lack of it will forever control you.</Quote>
    <Author>Dave Ramsey</Author>
  </FinanceQuote>
  <FinanceQuote>
    <Quote>It's not how much money you make, but how much money you keep, how hard it works for you, and how many generations you keep it for.</Quote>
    <Author>Robert Kiyosaki</Author>
  </FinanceQuote>
  <FinanceQuote>
    <Quote>The successful warrior is the average man, with laser-like focus.</Quote>
    <Author>Bruce Lee</Author>
  </FinanceQuote>
  <FinanceQuote>
    <Quote>A journey of a thousand miles must begin with a single step.</Quote>
    <Author>Lao Tzu</Author>
  </FinanceQuote>
  <FinanceQuote>
    <Quote>The best thing money can buy is financial freedom.</Quote>
    <Author>Me</Author>
  </FinanceQuote>
  <FinanceQuote>
    <Quote>If we command our wealth, we shall be rich and free. If our wealth commands us, we are poor indeed.</Quote>
    <Author>Edmund Burke</Author>
  </FinanceQuote>
</QuotesCollection>
